Thomas C. O'Donnell Papers
Thomas Clay O'Donnell Papers
- Writings, published
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 7)
Peterson, Dutton S. Dec 30, 1957 (to) Dec 31, 1957 (from) Sep 11, 1958 (from) Sep 12, 1958 (to) Sep 30, 1958 (to) Oct 30, 1958 (to) Oct 20, 1958 (to) Nov 21, 1958 (from) Nov 21, 1958 (to) Nov 25, 1958 (from) Dec 2, 1958 (from) Oct 8, 1960 (from) Oct 18, 1960 (to) Oct 21, 1960 (from) Oct 24, 1960 (to) Jun 19, 1963 (from) Jun 26, 1963 (to) Oct 29, 1963 (from) Jan 17, 1964 (to)
Poulton, Fred N. May 3, 1965 (to) May 10, 1965 (from) May 10, 1965 (to) May 17, 1965 (to) May 20, 1965 (from) May 24, 1965 (to) Oct 4, 1965 (from) Oct 13, 1965 (to) Dec 6, 1965 (from) Nov 7, 1966 (from)
Powell, Lewis N. Jun 18, 1959 (from) Aug 19, 1959 (from) Aug 20, 1959 (to)
The Protestant Council of the City of New York Oct 8, 1965 (from)
Quinlivan, Dr. James J. Apr 15, 1957 (to)
Rishell, Paul W. Jan 30, 1957 (from) Feb 1, 1957 (to) Mar 10, 1965 (to) May 3, 1965 (from) Jun 17, 1965 (to) Jun 26, 1965 (from) Jul 2, 1965 (to) Aug 16, 1965 (to) Aug 28, 1965 (from) Sep 6, 1965 (from) Oct 16, 1965 (from) Oct 21, 1965 (to) Feb 7, 1966 (to) Feb 12, 1966 (from) Feb 17, 1966 (to) Mar 5, 1966 (from) Mar 12, 1966 (from) Mar 18, 1966 (to) May 3, 1966 (from) Sep 12, 1966 (from)
Roadarmel, Kenneth May 1, 1953 (from) May 22, 1953 (to) Nov 20, 1956 (from) Dec 5, 1957 (to)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. Dec 10, 1959 (to) Jan 18, 1960 (to) Dec 11, 1963 (to) Dec 26, 1963 (to) Jan 4, 1965 (to) Jan 7, 1965 (from) May 28, 1965 (to) Jun 14, 1965 (from) Jun 18, 1965 (to) Jun 23, 1965 (from) Jun 28, 1965 (from) Jul 7, 1965 (to) Aug 7, 1967 (from) Aug 14, 1967 (to) Aug 22, 1967 (from) Apr 8, 1968 (from) Apr 23, 1968 (to) May 17, 1968 (from)
Ronan, William J. Nov 17, 1960 (from)
Root, Oren Nov 17, 1960 (from)
Schrock, Robert C. Jan 11, 1963 (from) Jan 21, 1963 (to)
Scott, Philip Gordon Jan 5, 1962 (from) Jan 10, 1962 (to)
Smith, William E. Apr 1, 1959 (from) Apr 7, 1959 (to) Dec 30, 1959 (from) Jan 5, 1960 (from)
Sockman, Ralph Jun 2, 1958 (to) Aug 18, 1958 (to) Oct 31, 1958 (to) Nov 7, 1958 (from) Nov 18, 1958 (to) Nov 21, 1958 (from) Nov 28, 1958 (to) Dec 8, 1958 (to)
Stevenson, Adlai E. Nov 14, 1960 (from) Nov 14, 1960 (to)
Strohbeck, Charles W. Feb 14, 1967 (from) Feb 21, 1967 (to)
Terry, John H. Apr 7, 1966 (from) Apr 22, 1966 (to) Dec 27, 1966 (from) Jan 5, 1967 (to) Jan 17, 1967 (to)
Tobin, Charles J. Jr. Jun 28, 1963 (to) Jul 2, 1963 (from)
Travia, Anthony J. Jan 10, 1959 (to) Jan 3, 1966 (to) Mar 28, 1966 (to) May 13, 1966 (to)
Twentieth Century Fund Jun 18, 1958 (from) Jun 24, 1958 (to) Jun 30, 1958 (from) Jul 5, 1958 (to) Jul 10, 1958 (from) Jul 15, 1958 (to) Jul 16, 1958 (to)
Wagner, Robert F. Aug 30, 1967 (from)
Ward, W. Ralph Sep 24, 1964 (from) Dec 16, 1964 (from) Dec 21, 1964 (to)
Webb, James M. Apr 20, 1965 (to)
Westchester Citizens Committee of the National Council on Crime and Delinquency Mar 9, 1965 (from) Oct 15, 1965 (from) Oct 20, 1965 (to)
Whitehead, A. Pennington Sep 24, 1953 (from) Sep 30, 1953 (to) Oct 2, 1953 (from) Oct 15, 1953 (to) Oct 19, 1953 (from) Nov 11, 1953 (to) Nov 12, 1953 (from) Mar 10, 1954 (to) Mar 10, 1954 (from) Mar 11, 1954 (from) Mar 24, 1954 (from) Apr 6, 1954 (to) Apr 7, 1954 (from)
Wiediger, Edward H. Apr 27, 1966 (from) May 2, 1966 (to)
Wilson, Jerome L. Dec 24, 1958 (to) Feb 19, 1965 (to) Jan 3, 1966 (to) Apr 25, 1966 (from)
Selected index to correspondence - Topics
Abortion Feb 14, 1967 Feb 21, 1967
Aging Dec 10, 1959 Dec 23, 1959 Jul 8, 1960 Jul 12, 1960 Jul 29, 1960 Aug 3, 1960 Dec 1, 1967
Alcoholic Beverage Control Sep 23, 1958 Jan 11, 1963 Jan 21, 1963 Jun 19, 1963 Jun 26, 1963 Jun 28, 1963 Jul 2, 1963 Aug 1, 1963 Aug 2, 1963 Aug 4, 1963 Aug 9, 1963 Oct 29, 1963 Nov 20, 1963 Aug 14, 1964 Aug 25, 1964
Baptist Commission Oct 28, 1954 Nov 1, 1954 Jun 14, 1956 Oct 29, 1956 Oct 31, 1956 Nov 30, 1956 Dec 5, 1956 Dec 26, 1956 Jan 7, 1957 Jan 18, 1957 Jan 22, 1957 Mar 8, 1958 Mar 14, 1958 Mar 20, 1958 Mar 25, 1958 Aug 8, 1958 Aug 12, 1958
Birth control Jun 9, 1959
Champlain Valley 350th (1963) Jun 18, 1959 Jul 15, 1959 Aug 19, 1959 Aug 20, 1959
Church-State, Parochial Schools Apr 1, 1959 Apr 7, 1959
Churchmen's International May 3, 1965 May 10, 1965 May 17, 1965 May 20, 1965 May 24, 1965 Oct 4, 1965 Oct 13, 1965 Dec 6, 1965 Nov 7, 1966
Civilian Defense Chaplains May 22, 1953 Jul 16, 1953 Jul 22, 1953 Aug 13, 1953 Aug 14, 1953 Nov 12, 1953
Constitutional Convention Jun 22, 1966 Jun 23, 1966 Jun 27, 1966 Jul 27, 1966 Aug 2, 1966 Nov 14, 1966 Nov 22, 1966 Nov 28, 1966 Nov 29, 1966 Dec 29, 1966 Feb 6, 1967 Feb 21, 1967 Feb 28, 1967 Mar 21, 1967 Mar 27, 1967 Apr 12, 1967 Apr 25, 1967 Apr 26, 1967 May 1, 1967 May 2, 1967 May 5, 1967 May 8, 1967 May 10, 1967 May 12, 1967 May 15, 1967 May 16, 1967 Jul 5, 1967 Jul 17, 1967 Jul 24, 1967 Jul 25, 1967 Aug 3, 1967 Aug 6, 1967 Aug 10, 1967 Aug 14, 1967 Aug 30, 1967 Sep 21, 1967 Sep 26, 1967 Oct 14, 1967
Cooperstown Proposal Jan 26, 1953 Jan 30, 1953 May 1, 1953 Sep 24, 1953 Sep 30, 1953 Oct 2, 1953 Oct 15, 1953 Oct 19, 1953 Nov 11, 1953 Nov 12, 1953 Dec 26, 1953 Jan 15, 1954 Jan 20, 1954 Jan 26, 1954 Mar 10, 1954 Mar 11, 1954 Mar 24, 1954 Apr 6, 1954 Apr 7, 1954
Denominational-Interdenominational Sep 24, 1964 Oct 2, 1964 Dec 16, 1964 Dec 21, 1964
Family justice Oct 1, 1965 Oct 13, 1965
Finance promotion data Feb 7, 1955 Mar 30, 1956 Apr 3, 1956 Dec 31, 1956 Jan 9, 1957 Dec 22, 1958 Dec 14, 1959
Home Advisory Council of New York, Inc. Feb 2, 1956
Hospital employees Mar 9, 1963 Mar 11, 1963 Mar 12, 1963 Mar 20, 1963 Mar 21, 1963
Human Rights Commission Aug 7, 1967 Aug 14, 1967 Aug 22, 1967 Aug 24, 1967 Apr 8, 1968 Apr 23, 1968 May 17, 1968
Legislative Commissions Jan 10, 1959 Jan 29, 1963 Jan 7, 1965 Jan 8, 1965 Jan 9, 1965 Jan 10, 1965 Jan 21, 1965 Jan 25, 1965 Jan 28, 1965 Feb 9, 1965 Mar 3, 1965 Mar 9, 1965 Mar 10, 1965 Apr 5, 1965 Apr 9, 1965 Apr 10, 1965 Apr 12, 1965 Apr 15, 1965 Apr 20, 1965 May 24, 1965 May 25, 1965 May 28, 1965 Jun 1, 1965 Jun 4, 1965 Jun 7 1965 Jun 10, 1965 Jun 12, 1965 Jun 14, 1965 Jun 15, 1965 Jun 17, 1965 Jun 18, 1965 Jun 21, 1965 Jun 22, 1965 Jun 23, 1965 Jun 28, 1965 Jul 6, 1965 Jul 7, 1965 Aug 26, 1965 Aug 30, 1965 Sep 10, 1965 Sep 14, 1965 Sep 17, 1965 Sep 22, 1965 Sep 29, 1965 Oct 8, 1965 Oct 13, 1965 Oct 15, 1965 Oct 20, 1965 Oct 21, 1965 Oct 25, 1965 Oct 29, 1965 Nov 4, 1965 Dec 23, 1965 Dec 31, 1965 Jan 3, 1966 Jan 5, 1966 Feb 4, 1966 Feb 7, 1966 Feb 14, 1966 Feb 17, 1966 Feb 28, 1966 Mar 1, 1966 Mar 12, 1966 Mar 21, 1966 Mar 28, 1966 Apr 4, 1966 Apr 6, 1966 Apr 7, 1966 Apr 22, 1966 Apr 25, 1966 May 2, 1966 May 5, 1966 May 6, 1966 May 13, 1966 May 26, 1966 Jun 6, 1966 Jun 13, 1966 Jun 27, 1966 Jun 28, 1966 Aug 18, 1966 Aug 23, 1966
Legislative Seminars Jan 13, 1956 Dec 30, 1957 Dec 31, 1957 Dec 1, 1958 Dec 8, 1958 Dec 11, 1958 Dec 17, 1958 Dec 20, 1958 Dec 23, 1958 Dec 31, 1958 Jul 17, 1959 Jul 24, 1959 Nov 24, 1959 Nov 30, 1959 Dec 4, 1959 Dec 9, 1959 Dec 17, 1959 Dec 21, 1959 Jan 18, 1960 Oct 8, 1960 Oct 18, 1960 Oct 21, 1960 Oct 24, 1960 Nov 14, 1960 Nov 15, 1960 Nov 17, 1960 Dec 7, 1960 Dec 12, 1960 Dec 29, 1960 Jan 4, 1961 Jan 9, 1961 Jan 10, 1961 Dec 22, 1961 May 28, 1962 Jun 5, 1962 Jun 8, 1962 Jun 12, 1962 Jan 18, 1963 Jan 28, 1963 Feb 4, 1963 Apr 23, 1963 Jun 28, 1963 Jul 3, 1963 Sep 3, 1963 Oct 6, 1963 Oct 11, 1963 Dec 4, 1963 Dec 11, 1963 Dec 18, 1963 Dec 26, 1963 Jan 16, 1964 Jan 17, 1964 Sep 14, 1964 Sep 17, 1964 Sep 29, 1964 Oct 29, 1964 Nov 12, 1964 Dec 29, 1964 Jan 4, 1965 Feb 19, 1965 Sep 13, 1967 Dec 19, 1969
Lottery Mar 10, 1965 May 3, 1965 Jun 17, 1965 Jun 26, 1965 Jul 2, 1965 Aug 16, 1965 Aug 28, 1965 Sep 6, 1965 Oct 16, 1965 Oct 21, 1965 Dec 20, 1965 Feb 7, 1966 Feb 12, 1966 Feb 17, 1966 Mar 5, 1966 Mar 7, 1966 Mar 10, 1966 Mar 11, 1966 Mar 14, 1966 Mar 17, 1966 Mar 21, 1966 Apr 27, 1966 May 2, 1966 Jun 30, 1966 Jul 5, 1966 Jul 30, 1966 Aug 1, 1966 Aug 5, 1966 Aug 16, 1966 (repro. of letter to A. Milain Smith, Lottery-Comm. of 100,000 Against the Lottery) Sep 12, 1966 Oct 13, 1966
Lottery, Committee of 100,000 Dec 20, 1966 Dec 27, 1966 Dec 29, 1966 Jan 5, 1967 Jan 10, 1967 Jan 17, 1967
Lottery, State Commission Against Feb 18, 1966 Mar 8, 1966 Mar 12, 1966 Mar 18, 1966 May 3, 1966 May 19, 1966 May 27, 1966 May 31, 1966 Jun 8, 1966 Jun 27, 1966 Jul 5, 1966 Jul 12, 1966 Jul 14, 1966 Jul 21, 1966 Jul 22, 1966 Jul 26, 1966 Jul 27, 1966 Jul 29, 1966 Jul 30, 1966 Aug 2, 1966 Aug 3, 1966 Aug 8, 1966 Aug 12, 1966 Aug 26, 1966 Sep 1, 1966 Sep 7, 1966 Sep 8, 1966 Sep 12, 1966 Sep 13, 1966 Sep 14, 1966 Sep 15, 1966 Sep 19, 1966 Sep 28, 1966
Matrimonial and family laws Dec 30, 1959 Jan 5, 1960
Meetings, Annual Assembly Jan 27, 1960 May 13, 1960 May 26, 1960 Jun 13, 1960 Jun 16, 1960 Jun 29, 1960 Jul 26, 1960 Nov 14, 1960 Nov 18, 1960 Nov 23, 1960 Dec 2, 1960 Nov 22, 1961 Jan 5, 1962 Jan 10, 1962
Meetings, Trustees Apr 8, 1954 Apr 12, 1954
Narcotics Dec 5, 1960
New York Board of Rabbis Sep 11, 1958 Sep 12, 1958 Sep 30, 1958 Nov 21, 1958
One Hundred Club Jun 2, 1958 Aug 18, 1958 Oct 20, 1958 Oct 30, 1958 Oct 31, 1958 Nov 7, 1958 Nov 18, 1958 Nov 21, 1958 Nov 25, 1958 Nov 28, 1958 Dec 2, 1958 Dec 8, 1958 Dec 24, 1958
Obscene literature Oct 23, 1961
Prayer in the schools Jan 16, 1964 Feb 6, 1964 Feb 19, 1964 Feb 28, 1964 Mar 23, 1964 Apr 7, 1964
Public Relations & Development Sep 26, 1955 Nov 20, 1956 Dec 5, 1957 Jun 18, 1958 Jun 24, 1958 Jun 30, 1958 Jul 5, 1958 Jul 10, 1958 Jul 15, 1958 Jul 16, 1958 Dec 31, 1958
Roswell Park Mar 11, 1957 Mar 16, 1957 Mar 22, 1957 Mar 26, 1957 Apr 1, 1957 Apr 15, 1957
Study Committee Jun 7, 1960 Jun 10, 1960
Youth in the courts Jan 30, 1957 Feb 1, 1957